Inspired by Karpathy
I spent half an hour
vibecoded an RSS reader
you can see all the blogs
And it updates information daily.
I also added three features to it
AI-generated summaries and Chinese translation
and discuss with it in the AI window using a large model
A few days ago, Karpathy posted on X, formerly known as Twitter, saying
He found that websites are now flooded with a lot of useless junk information
especially regarding AI news
He himself is also using RSS more and more frequently
Here lies high-quality long-form content.
rather than those provocative, false and exaggerated contents
He also urged that we should restore RSS as soon as possible.
because it's open and customizable
He recommended in the post that we can download an RSS reader
You can download the client
or customize one yourself through vibecoding
He also provided a link
This link contains the 92 most popular blogs in 2025
RSS feed list
Perhaps many people, like me,
also not quite understand what RSS is
It's somewhat similar to an electronic newspaper box
which blog you subscribed to
It delivers new articles to you every day
to your RSS reader
Just like delivering to your mailbox
You don't need to jump to other websites
You can complete all your article reading right within the reader
You can also star mark good articles
build your own knowledge base
So today in this video I'd like to share how I
How to handcraft and deploy this RSS reader
How to import information from GitHub
how to use it daily, these three aspects to share
The tool I use for vibeCODING is Google AI Studio
I think it's the most suitable for beginners
Because it can help you using natural language
you create the tool you want
Modifications during the process are also made using natural language, and the final output has a visually appealing front-end interface.
After opening Google AI Studio
Click on this build
build is for creating this type of application, and this area is for development
Before we do anything
We need to configure the API key first
It is essentially a key
It can unlock Gemini and all Google
a gateway to AI permissions
Of course, using this key costs money.
every time you call Google's AI functions
it will deduct money from your account
We click to open
Actually, I've already configured an API key here
If you want to obtain it
If you want to create one
There is a 'Create API Key' option in the upper right corner
click
You can name it
Then select the project to import
You can create a new project
For example, project03, create a project
So your API key is under this project, specifically for this reader
We create the key
Look, this is what we just created
Set up billing information for it
Because if you design it as a free tier
Many features are unavailable to you.
Let's set up the payment information
Add billing account
This is one of Me accounts
Settings completed
If you just couldn't select
like this first in Me
because you haven't set up a billing account in the Google Cloud console
You need to click on this Google Cloud billing console
Look, this is what I created
If you don't have an account here
You need to click on 'Create Account' first, and as for the payment method
You need to add it here
Since I've already added it
so I'll just submit and
Enable the billing function and you're good to go
If you don't have one
You need to use a Visa card to submit it
After the configuration is complete
Let's go back to this Google AI Studio
back to our build
If your English is not particularly good
If you want to switch between Chinese and English
as usual
Click on the immersive translation at the top of this browser
Just translate it
you'll understand
what all this does
You just normally input your idea in this 'describe your idea' section
Just input what you want it to do
I actually wanted it to create a local client at the very beginning
so I told Me my computer model
as well as my goal, I told him what I wanted to achieve
This is my prompt
Then he started to think about building the architecture
writing code
This process will take approximately 3 minutes.
Then you will see the Preview on the right side
it will display the already built interface, and you can proceed with testing
For example, I click this 'upload source' button
paste it in here
Then you click on each channel
You'll find that no content is displayed
No content will be displayed even if you click refresh
Its functionality currently has some flaws
I then described this issue to the AI in the left chat window
Continue adjusting and fixing
Repeat the previous step to test
This time it refreshed and displayed all the content source links.
but I noticed many contents are only partially displayed
incomplete display
I need to click on this view to see the full content
original source
I don't want this
I'll go back to the chat window and tell him
I want to directly view it in this reader
can see the full content inside
Adding two more features would make it more convenient
one is AI summarization
one is AI chat
Soon he had it ready again
This time, ensuring all functions work properly while
also added an AI summarization feature
Click on AI and it will summarize what this article is about
but I found its summary incomplete
Continue posting this issue in the chat window
tell it to modify
and send him a screenshot of the problematic part
The AI summary feature is working properly now.
Additionally, a discuss button has been added.
I can discuss in this window with the Gemini-based
the model to discuss this article
question
Now the basic features I wanted are all implemented
But the page isn't that aesthetically pleasing yet
For example, when I'm chatting with the AI
Other windows are taking up too much space
I need a button that can collapse unused idle windows.
After making the modifications
This feature was quickly implemented.
In addition to the previous features
I also added a translation feature
can translate English into Chinese
Just click here
Because all these recommended by Karpathy
the articles are basically all in English
we find it a bit difficult to read
With this conversion, it becomes much easier to use.
But this consumes a lot of TOKENS
For example, I tried twice
he finally helped me successfully implement this function
He implemented some optimization solutions, how smart!
You just need to tell him what result you want
As for the specific methods, he will figure them out.
If you like this article
You can click a star
You can find it in this starred section
you find
Then all the articles you've favorited will appear here
For example, if I select another article and like this one
I'll bookmark it with a star
Here are two articles now.
Over time, these will all be articles you like
You can periodically organize and summarize it
as well as sharing your thoughts
You can store it here as your own Knowledge base.
Because this tool was just developed today,
More features can be added in the future
For example, all the content you've starred
aggregate into a single window
Generate a new article
With AI, all these functions can be achieved.
Finally, it's time for deployment. Here, there's a symbol that looks like a clock.
Click on this, and you can see all the historical versions
a few hours ago
what changes you asked it to make
It's all saved here
If you find that things have gotten messed up
you want to return to the previous version
then you can use this feature to perform the rollback
If you want to deploy it,
For You
If you're a beginner
you want to boost your confidence
just use Google's native, built-in deployment app
Click to select a project
Because I've already deployed it once before.
If I want to redeploy it again
I'll click this re-deploy APP
Then it will redeploy for me again
Actually, deploying on Google has both advantages and disadvantages
The advantage is simplicity—it's a one-click deployment.
You don't need to worry about your API being exposed on the website and being taken by others
and consume your credits
It is highly secure
Google has a security system
is to protect your API
The downside is, you can't switch to other large models
All the features we are currently developing
are all based on the Gemini model
But if you want to switch to Claude
You can't switch to OpenAI
Because it's a pre-packaged system
That's why Google made it easy
you're relying on its model
it won't be easy for you to switch later
For us beginners
We just want to practice first
Get it done first
so we just use whatever is simplest to get it done first
and then gradually explore those more complex ones
then enter this URL in the browser address bar
This way you can get in
this URL
So when you want to use this again in the future
without having to go into Google AI Studio every time
press a bunch of buttons to open it
it's quite convenient
Remember to like, favorite, share and Follow!